Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Family and Personal Papers, 1841-2000 MS 252
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Family, 207785 (Box 1-15)
  - Subseries F: John T. Jones, 208128 (Box 12)
    - Insurance, 208179 (Box 13)
      - Missouri State Life, 1925-43; 208192 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Northwestern National Life, 1930-46; 208193 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Ocean Accident and Life, 1928-37; 208194 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Praetorians, 1925-43; 208195 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - San Jacinto Life, 1930-32; 208196 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Seaboard Life, 1928-45; 208197 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Southland Life, 1931-46; 208198 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Southwestern Life, 1908-46; 208199 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Texas Life, 1932-46; 208200 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Traveler's Group, 1942; 208201 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Income tax (Box 14)
      - 1923 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - 1924 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - 1925 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - 1926 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - 1927 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - 1928 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - 1929 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - 1930 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - 1931 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - 1932-33 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - 1934-35 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - 1936 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - 1937 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - 1938 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - 1939 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - 1940 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - 1941 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - 1942 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - 1943 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - 1944 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - 1945-46 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - 1947-49 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - 1950-53 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Subseries G: Mary Gibbs Jones, 208226 (Box 15)
    - Biographical, 208227 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings, 208228 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Certificates, 208229 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Engagement book, 1921; 208230 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Personal property-jewelry and furs, 1922-53; 208231 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Invitations, 208232 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Shiplaunch-S.S. James Madison, 1942; 208233 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Publicity, 1942-58; 208234 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Portrait-St. Paul's Methodist Church, 1957; 208235 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Portrait-Texas Woman's University, 1961; 208236 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Poems, 208237 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Library of Congress materials, 1957-61; 208238 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 208239 (Box 15)
      - 1918-63, 208240 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Eisenhowers, 208241 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - F. Heyne, 1955-59; 208242 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Jesse H. Jones, 1903-47; 208243 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Augusta Jones, 1915; 208244 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Washington, DC, 1930s-40s; 208245 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Eleanor Roosevelt, 1930s, 40; 208246 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Betty Rogers, 1935; 208247 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Edith Wilson, 1920s-30s, 1950s-60; 208248 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Houston Club, 1933-57; 208249 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Subseries H: Family research, 210037 (Box 15)
    - Byron Welch, researcher, 210038 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Robert Wilson/Sarah Deel leagues, Webster Farms Co., 1830; 210039 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - James Holman indenture, 1837; 210041 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Family graves, TN, ca. 1915; 210045 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Series II: Personal (JHJ), 208250 (Box 16-92)
  - Subseries A: Life cycle, 210665 (Box 16)
    - Biographies, 210666 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings [see also realia box 79], 210667 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Passport, 1952; 210668 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Surgery, 1953; 210669 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Auto accident, 1911; 210670 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York trip, 1905; 210680 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Move from Washington, DC to Houston, TX, 1947; 210681 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - St. Paul's Methodist Church Building Committee, 1911-17; 210682 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Wills, 210671 (Box 16)
      - 1899, 210672 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - 1902, 210673 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - 1904, 210674 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - 1905, 210675 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - 1909, 210676 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - 1950; codicil 1953, 210677 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Obituaries [see also audio/visual boxes 91-92], 1956; 210678 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Resolutions on death, 1956; 210679 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Subseries B: Residences, 208271 (Box 16)
    - Rice Hotel, Houston, TX, 1899, 1904; 208272 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Rice Hotel apartment keys, 1923; 208273 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Lamar Hotel apartment, Houston, TX [see also Lamar Hotel plate-box 84], 1927; 208274 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - The Mayflower apartment, Washington, DC, 1933; 208275 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Subseries C: Correspondence, 208317 (Box 16)
    - Christmas card samples, 208318 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - re: Christmas grapefruit, 1928, 33; 208319 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Crew & Co. Publishers, 1911-12; 208320 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - re: Forest Park Cemetery plots, 1958; 208321 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - re: poker chips, 208322 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Yachts, 1933; 208323 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Fifty Billion Dollars/Edward Angly, 1953-60; 208381 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Jesse Jones biography/Bascom Timmons, 1956-63; 208382 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Stationery samples, 210683 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Subseries D: Commemorations, 208779 (Box 16)
    - Will Rogers commemorative float, 1935; 208780 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Will Rogers statue, 1939; 208781 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Woodrow Wilson memorial service, 1924; 208782 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Subseries E: Financial, 1955; 208328 (Box 17)
    - Personal expenses, 1925-38; 208316 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Receipts, 1955; 208783 (Box 17)
      - 1908-13, 208872 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - 1955, 208873 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Check register, 1950s; 208325 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Poll tax, 1908-17; 208784 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Taxes, ca. 1910; 210054 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - National Bank of Commerce issued currency, 208818 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Financial statement, 1921; 208867 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Accounts, 208869 (Box 17)
      - 1904-07, 208870 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - 1910, 208871 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Assets, 1911; 208874 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Investments, 208875 (Box 17)
        - 1910-13, 208876 (Box 17, Folder 15)
        - 1929-42, 208877 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Petty cash, 208878 (Box 17)
        - 1942-55, 208879 (Box 17, Folder 17)
        - 1953, 208880 (Box 17, Folder 18)
        - 1955-89, 208881 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Estate bills, 1956; 208882 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Notes receivable, 208845 (Box 17)
      - Index, 208846 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - 1897, 208847 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - 1902-06, 208848 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - 1908-09, 208849 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - 1908-10, 208850 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - 1911-12, 208851 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - M.E. Foster, 1914-26; 208852 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - 1920-24, 208853 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - 1925-55, 208854 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Notes payable, 208855 (Box 18)
      - 1902-09, 208856 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - 1910-11, 208857 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - 1912-16, 208858 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - 1917-23, 208859 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - H.S.H. Wilson & H.T.D. Wilson, 208860 (Box 18)
      - Notes 1907-14, 208861 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Notes 1910-16, 208862 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Notes 1912, 208863 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Notes 1912-14, 208864 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Notes 1912-15, 208865 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Notes paid off in settlement, 1913; 208866 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Agreement, 1910; 208883 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Estate, 1922; 208884 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Ledgers [see boxes 87-90], 210746 (Box 87-90)
  - Subseries F: Honors, 208754 (Box 18-19)
    - Texas state portrait, 208820 (Box 18-19)
      - Senate resolution, 1935; 208821 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Negotiations, 1935; 208822 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Invitations, 1935; 208823 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Guest list, 1935; 208824 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Unveiling acknowledgments, 208825 (Box 19)
        - A-B, 1935; 208826 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - C, 1935; 208827 (Box 19, Folder 2)
        - D-F, 1935; 208828 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - G-H, 1935; 208829 (Box 19, Folder 4)
        - I-K, 1935; 208830 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        - L-M, 1935; 208831 (Box 19, Folder 6)
        - N-P, 1935; 208832 (Box 19, Folder 7)
        - R-S, 1935; 208833 (Box 19, Folder 8)
        - T-V, 1935; 208834 (Box 19, Folder 9)
        - W-Y, 1935; 208835 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Speech, 1935; 208836 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Newsclippings, 1935; 208837 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence -Mary G. Jones, 1935; 208838 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Pamphlet, 1935; 208839 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Replacement (and Mary Gibbs Jones'), 1961; 208841 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Certificates and accolades, 1939-42; 208840 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - No-tsu-oh, 1911-13; 208281 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Honorary degrees, 1942-54; 208842 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Southland Foundation [memorial] scholarships, 1956; 208843 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Pantheon of Philanthropy, 1979; 208844 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Man of the Hour and Year 1928 [see box 83], 210687 (Box 83)
    - California Commission Golden Gate International Exposition appreciation plaque [see box 83], 210688 (Box 83)
    - Testimonials honoring JHJ, 208664 (Box 19)
      - Dallas, 208665 (Box 19)
        - 1928, 208666 (Box 19, Folder 21)
        - 1933, 208667 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Ft. Worth, 208668 (Box 19)
        - 1927, 208669 (Box 19, Folder 23)
        - 1928, 208670 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Houston, 208671 (Box 19)
        - 1914, 208672 (Box 19, Folder 25)
        - 1923, 208673 (Box 19, Folder 26-27)
        - 1928, 208674 (Box 19, Folder 28)
        - 1933, 208675 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - 1934, 208676 (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - 1942, 208677 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - 1954, 208678 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - New York, 1943; 208679 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Texas A&M University, 208680 (Box 20)
        - 1936, 208681 (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - 1939, 208682 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Subseries G: Personal property, 208922 (Box 20-21)
    - Automobiles, 208923 (Box 20)
      - 1909 Waverly Electric, 1909-10; 208924 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - 1910 Packard, 1910-12; 208925 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - 1910 Pierce Arrow, 208926 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - 1921 Cadillac Limousine, 208927 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - 1922 Pierce Arrow Limousine, 208928 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - 1926 Lincoln Broughm, 208929 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - 1938 Cadillac Imperial, 208930 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Cadillacs, 1941-49; 208931 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - 1949 Cadillac Fleetwood, 208932 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - 1952 Ford convertible, 208933 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Boats, 208934 (Box 20)
      - Elco Deluxe Cruiser, 1947; 208935 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Chris Craft Express Cruiser "Audrey", 208936 (Box 20)
        - 1948-49, 208937 (Box 20, Folder 19)
        - 1950-51, 208938 (Box 20, Folder 20)
        - 1952-54, 208939 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Lamar Hotel apartment contents, 1945-60; 208940 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Art works, 1917-55; 208941 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Phonograph records, ca. 1920; 208942 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Subseries H: Stocks and bonds, 208364 (Box 20)
    - Stocks, 208365 (Box 20)
      - A-B, 208366 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - C-E, 208367 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - F-G, 208368 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - H-J, 208369 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - L-M, 208370 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - N-P, 208371 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Q-S, 208372 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - T-V, 208373 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - W-Z, 208374 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Houston Lighting & Power Co., 1925; 208943 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - St. Paul's Methodist Church, 1917; 208944 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Southern Pacific Co., 1916; 208945 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Bonds, 208375 (Box 21)
      - Liberty, 208377 (Box 21)
        - ca. 1915, 208946 (Box 21, Folder 12)
        - 1918, 208947 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - 1955, 208378 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - U.S. Defense, 1941-53; 208948 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Inventory of bonds and coins, 1907; 208949 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Subseries I: Insurance, 208437 (Box 21)
    - Aetna, 1925-51; 208438 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - American General, 1931-52; 208439 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - American National, 1925-51; 208440 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Equitable Life, 208441 (Box 22)
      - #1258409, 1904-51; 208442 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - #1297967, 1904-51; 208443 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - #1312576, 208444 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - #1498703, 1906-47; 208445 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Fidelity, 1903; 208446 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Franklin, 1919-50; 208447 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - General American, 208448 (Box 22)
      - #230546, 1920-47; 208449 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - #373246, 1922-51; 208450 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Great Southern, 208451 (Box 22)
      - #835, 1910-53; 208452 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - #1837, 1918; 208453 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - #30053, 1918-52; 208454 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - #29967, 1918-52; 208455 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - #62431, 1921-52; 208456 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - #67661, 1921-52; 208457 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - #30319, 1932-52; 208458 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - #27518, 1933-42; 208459 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Guarantee Life, 1908-16; 208460 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Kansas City Life, 1911-50; 208461 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Northwestern National, 1920-48; 208462 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Pioneer American, 1930-47; 208463 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Praetorians, 1925-55; 208464 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Provident, 208465 (Box 23)
      - #177550-52, 1908; 208466 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - #177548-49, 1908; 208467 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Seaboard, 1945; 208468 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Southland, 1932-56; 208469 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Southwestern, 208470 (Box 23)
      - #270453, 1931-49; 208471 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - #270221, 1932-47; 208472 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - #270222, 1932-49; 208473 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Houston Chronicle, 1931-39; 208474 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Houston Chronicle, 1940-41; 208475 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - State Life, 208476 (Box 23)
      - #302544, 1924-51; 208477 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - #302440, 1924-52; 208478 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Union Central, 208479 (Box 23)
      - #689101, 1922-52; 208480 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - #689102, 1922-50; 208481 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - #855727, 1926-49; 208482 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - #855728, 1926-49; 208483 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - West Coast Life, 1930-54; 208484 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Life-misc., 1924-33; 208485 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Assignments to Houston Endowment, 1947; 208486 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Assignments to Houston Endowment, 1947-53; 208487 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Subseries J: Memberships, 208488 (Box 24)
    - List of club dues, 1930; 208489 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Allegro, 1925-27; 208490 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Beach Club, 1933; 208491 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - B.P.O. Elks, 1933-34; 208492 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Bay City Game Preserve Hunting Club, 1928-29; 208493 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Blind Brook Club, 1932-34; 208494 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the U.S., 1954-55; 208495 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Commerce Quarter Century Club, 1947; 208582 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Cork Club, 1956; 208496 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - East Texas Chamber of Commerce, 1926-53; 208497 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Essex Country Club, 1933; 208498 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Exalted Order of the Giraffe, 1945; 208499 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Exchange Club of Ft. Worth, 1928; 208500 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Ft. Worth Club, 1931; 208501 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Glenbrook Country Club, 1923-27; 208502 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Gridiron Club, 1928; 208503 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Houston Baseball Association, 1933; 208504 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Houston Chamber of Commerce, 1954; 208505 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Houston City Athletic Club, 1933; 208506 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Houston Club, 1953-59; 208507 (Box 24, Folder 21-22)
    - Houston Country Club, 1906-56; 208508 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Houston Launch Club, 1926; 208509 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Houston Riding and Polo Club, 1927; 208510 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Jefferson Islands Club, 1931-33; 208511 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Lamar Club, 208512 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Lotos Club, 1933; 208513 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Loyal Order of Moose, 1933; 208514 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Manhattan Club, 1933; 208515 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - North Conway Golf Club, 1941; 208516 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Petroleum Club, 1952; 208517 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - River Oaks Country Club, 1954-55; 208518 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Salesmanship Club, 1933; 208519 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Seabrook Yacht Club, 1916; 208520 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Tax Foundation, Inc., 1958; 208521 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Texas Heritage Foundation, Inc., 1957; 208522 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Thousand Islands Club, 1941; 208523 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Subseries K: Business, 208524 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence: controversies, 1928; 208606 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Private telegraphic code, 1910; 208607 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - National Opera Co. of Canada, 1914; 208608 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - National Bank of Commerce, 1921; 208609 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - New York Trust Co., 1921-22; 208610 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Corporate organization, 1933; 208611 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Houston Terminal Land Co., 208612 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Commercial National Bank lease, 1907; 208613 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1925-26; 208641 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Banking related, 210055 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Building construction, 210056 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Hotel related, 210057 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - KTRH, 210058 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Houston Chronicle editorial policy, 1952; 208642 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Property holdings, 1912 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Legal, 208643 (Box 25)
      - Estates, 208644 (Box 25)
        - T.W. House, 1909; 208645 (Box 25, Folder 16)
        - Phoebe McKinnon, 1911; 208646 (Box 25, Folder 17)
        - Lula Roland Packard, 1913-14; 208647 (Box 25, Folder 18)
        - George Hermann property trade, 1918; 208648 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Taylor settlement, 1913; 208649 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Powers of Attorney, 208650 (Box 25)
        - N.E. Meador, 1910; 208651 (Box 25, Folder 21)
        - Meador, Heyne, Jones, 1933, 55; 208652 (Box 25, Folder 22)
        - Real estate reorganization, 1939; 208653 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Misc. documents, 1924-35; 208654 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - File indices, 1919-42; 208655 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Subseries L: Editorials, 208656 (Box 25)
    - 1923-28, 208660 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - 1928-29, 208661 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - 1930, 208662 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - 1931, 208663 (Box 26, Folder 1-4, Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Subseries M: Political, 208683 (Box 26)
    - ABA convention, 1927, 33; 208684 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - John Kirby campaign fund, 1926; 210059 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - H. Baldwin Rice campaign, 1910-11; 208685 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - H. Baldwin Rice campaign accounts, 1911; 208686 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Ben Campbell campaign, 1913; 208687 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Gov. Miriam Ferguson [see also map case drawer ], 1930, 33; 208380 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Legislation, 1933; 208379 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Democratic National Convention, Houston, TX, 1928; 208688 (Box 26)
      - Tickets, 1928; 208689 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Cancelled check, 1926; 208690 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Cancelled checks, 1928; 208691 (Box 26, Folder 14-16)
      - Public address system, 1928; 208692 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Clippings and releases, 1928; 208693 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Presidential nomination, 1928; 208694 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Subseries N: Public Service, 208699 (Box 26-56)
    - Houston Ship Channel, 208700 (Box 26)
      - 1911-12, 208701 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - 1914-33, 208702 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Hermann Park, Houston, TX, 1916-19; 208703 (Box 26-27)
      - 1916-19, 208706 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Sam Houston statue, 1925-26; 208707 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Shipping Board Emergency Fleet Corp., 1917; 208704 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - American Red Cross, 1917-27; 208705 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - East Texas Chamber of Commerce, 1931-33; 208708 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Texas Centennial, 1931-36; 208709 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Houston Association of Building Owners and Managers, 1934; 208710 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 208714 (Box 27-30)
      - Correspondence, 208716 (Box 27)
        - 1932-39, 208747 (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - "Amos & Andy", 1936; 208748 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Public statements, 208717 (Box 27)
        - 1933-36, 208727 (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - 1937-40, 208728 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Reports, 208715 (Box 27)
        - 1933-38, 208718 (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Examination of Accounts, 208719 (Box 27)
          - year ended Dec. 31, 1933, 208720 (Box 27)
          - year ended Dec. 31, 1934, 208721 (Box 27)
          - year ended Dec. 31, 1937, 208722 (Box 28)
          - year ended Dec. 31, 1938, 208723 (Box 28)
        - Chief Auditor, 208724 (Box 28)
          - close of business Dec. 31, 1934, 208725 (Box 28)
          - close of business Dec. 31, 1936, 208726 (Box 28)
          - close of business Dec. 31, 1937, 234489 (Box 28)
          - close of business Dec. 31, 1938, 208729 (Box 28)
          - close of business Dec. 31, 1939, 208730 (Box 28)
      - Travel, 208731 (Box 28-30)
        - 1934-35, 208732 (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - 1935, 208737 (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - 1936, 208734 (Box 29, Folder 1, Box 28, Folder 3)
        - California, 1936; 208735 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - 1937, 208736 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
        - 1938, 208738 (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
        - Europe, 1938; 208739 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - 1939, 208740 (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
        - California, 1939; 208741 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - 1940, 208742 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Telephone and telegraph, 208743 (Box 30)
        - 1932-36, 208744 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - 1937-40, 208745 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - 1941, 208746 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Poem by Franklin D. Roosevelt, 208749 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Resignation (JHJ), 1939; 208750 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Old Timers' Reunion, 1947; 208751 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Fifty Billion Dollars: My Thirteen Years with the RFC (1932-1945); inscribed copy by Jesse H. Jones to Ella Rice Winston, 208752 (Box 30)
      - Jesse H. Jones: The Man and the Statesman by Bascom N. Timmons, 1956; 208969 (Box 30)
    - Elliott Roosevelt loans, 1939-47; 208970 (Box 30-31)
      - 1939-41, 208971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Balance sheets-Texas State Network, Inc., 1939-45; 208973 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - "Papers of top pertinence", 1939-47; 208972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - 1942-43, 208974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - 1945-47, 208982 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Testimony, 1945; 208975 (Box 31)
        - Bureau of Internal Revenue, 1945; 208976 (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - David Baird, 1945; 208977 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Newsclippings, 1945; 208978 (Box 31)
        - June-August 1945, 208979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Sept. 1945, 208980 (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - Oct. 1945-1946, 208981 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Federal Loan Administrator, 1941-49; 208983 (Box 31)
      - Correspondence, 1939-41; 208712 (Box 31)
        - 1939-41, 210139 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - 1941, 210140 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Appointments, 1939; 208713 (Box 31, Folder 11)